Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/trinhnguyen-9ab4b51b9 (LinkedIn) www.behance.net/trinhnguyen610 (Portfolio)

Top Skills

Adobe Photoshop
Adobe Illustrator
Graphic Design

Trinh Nguyen

Senior UI-UX Designer

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

I'm Trinh, a Graphic - Web UI/UX Designer from HCM City, Vietnam.

I've graduated from the University of Architecture in HCM City. I had over 7 years of experience in Graphic and Web Design.

I love all the world of Graphic Design from Corporate Identity to web development, I like clean and modern styles.

As a perfectionist, I want to learn more about Creative Design Industry so I never stop learning, exploring and improving myself.

Experience

SHIFT ASIA

Senior UI-UX Designer

September 2021 - Present (3 years 7 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Urbn8 SJC

Senior UI-UX Designer-Lead Design

October 2020 - July 2022 (1 year 10 months)

Phường Thảo Điền, Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

- -Create & manage Libraries, Design Systems for our Platform.
- -Research UI-UX and improve current our Platform.
- -Create Prototypes to show the Ideas.
- -Training new designer.
- -Create & assign tasks for the team member.

Ryukyu Interactive Vietnam Senior Graphic Web Designer September 2017 - June 2020 (2 years 10 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Manage multiple projects with major corporate clients in Japan, analyze briefs, research & brainstorm (individually & with a team).

Page 1 of 3

- Create a new design for company websites, e-commerce sites, new product/ campaign landing pages from wireframes, mockups, prototypes, developer collaboration for final products - post-launch maintenance.
- Examine & renew existing websites' layout to improve the attractiveness, brand awareness & sales.
- Design digital advertising banners across channels.
- Participate in the company's app development projects: create user flow chart, modify wireframes & design finished prototypes for the development team.
- Had 3 months working in Okinawa Japan.
- Do Color Theory Workshop for team members.
- Train new designers, assign tasks.
- Decoration for office.
- Clients: Amazon Japan, Hard Rock, Union, Daihatsu, Blue Seal Ice-cream, Japan Airlines, UQ Mobile, We Chat. Suzuki, Toyota.

Mirum Agency Freelancer June 2017 - September 2017 (4 months) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Design Web for "Phát Đạt Project"
Worked directly with the Art Director.

Viivue Web Design Company Graphic Web Designer April 2014 - August 2017 (3 years 5 months) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

- Analyze briefs, research & brainstorm (individually & with a team).
- Create a Wireframe + site map
- Create a new design for company websites, e-commerce sites, new product/ campaign landing pages from wireframes, mockups, prototypes, developer collaboration for final products.
- Do Typography Workshop for team members.
- Train new designers.
- Decoration for office.
- Clients: Europe (Belgium, French), USA, Vietnam.

Education

Architectural University in Ho Chi Minh City

Bachelor's degree, Graphic Design · (2009 - 2014)